Topical files 1
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Topical files 1, 2.1.9.4
  - Maine Lumberjacks, 1938 - 1940; 4 (Box 1615)
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Vast land, Reindeer], 26
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Vast land, Reindeer], 27
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks:] Andrew Bahr driving 3 Teams Reindeer, 28
    - Verso: Andrew Bahr driving 3 Teams Reindeer, 28-verso
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Vast land, Reindeer], 29
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Reindeer], 30
    - [The Maine Lumberjacks: Reindeer], 31
  - Lowell Thomas - Marco Polo painting [color photograph], undated; 5 (Box 1615)
    - [Lowell Thomas standing in front of Marco Polo painting], 1
  - Haig, Connie and Sasha Mardikian, circa 1977; 6 (Box 1615)
    - Merry Christmas; Haig, Connie & Sasha Mardikian, 1
    - Verso: Mr. & Mrs. Mardikian [address], 1-verso
  - Richard Matt, circa 1970s; 7 (Box 1615)
    - [Color photo, Richard Matt? posing for a picture], 1
  - Toni Matt, 1954 - 1981; 8 (Box 1615)
    - [Toni Matt: Portrait of a girl], 1
    - [Toni Matt: Portrait of man], 2
    - Toni Matt, winner of the 1939 Open National Downhill Race at Mt. Hood, Oregon, 3
    - [Toni Matt skiing], 4
    - [Profile of Toni Matt (?)], 5
    - [Portrait of Toni Matt], 6
    - [Toni Matt: Man on skiis], 7
    - Jr. Nat'l Champ of Austria 1937; Toni Matt-who did the impossible., 8
    - Verso: Jr. Nat'l Champ of Austria 1937; Toni Matt-who did the impossible., 8-verso
    - [Man (Toni Matt?) skiing ], 9
    - Toni Matt, instructor at the Eastern Slope Ski School, is shown tuning up for giant slalom race to be held today on Cranmore Mountain, 10
    - [Man (Toni Matt?) skiing], 11
    - [Toni Matt: Portrait of a man], 12
  - Memorabilia, circa late 1930s - 1940s; 9 (Box 1615)
    - Note: Potential memorabilia for display cases, 1
    - [Memorabilia: Lowell Thomas sitting at desk], 2
  - Meriden Gravure Company, 1931; 10 (Box 1615)
    - [Meriden Gravure Company: Close-up of Lowell Thomas], 1
  - Hack Miller, circa 1970; 11 (Box 1615)
    - [Hack Miller: Lowell Thomas leaning on side of bridge], 1
  - Maynard Miller, undated; 12 (Box 1615)
    - LT- Ross McCord Miller + Maynard Miller, 1
    - Verso: LT- Ross McCord Miller + Maynard Miller, 1-verso
  - Namesakes, 1943 July 8 - 1947 June 28; 13 (Box 1615)
    - [Namesakes:]East Orange, NJ; Aug 1st 1946; Mrs Lois Thomas Thomas H. Thomas Lowell Thomas. He was 15 on Aug 7th 1946, 1
    - Verso: East Orange, NJ; Aug 1st 1946; Mrs Lois Thomas Thomas H. Thomas Lowell Thomas. He was 15 on Aug 7th 1946, 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of 3] Newark New York; June 28, 1947; P.O. Box 184; My Dear Mr. Thomas:- It is more than fifteen years since my husband and I wrote you asking your permission to name our infant son after you, 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of 3], 3
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 3 of 3], 4
    - [Namesakes:]Greetings to Lowell Thomas from Lowell Thomas, 5
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of 2] Cambridge Ohio July 8-'43; Dear Sir:- Enclosed find picture of a little Cambridge chap who is your namesake, 6
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of 2], 7
  - Namesakes, 1944 December 5 - 1977 January 17; 14 (Box 1615)
    - [Namesakes:]School name: Harrodsburg; City: Harrodsburg; State: KY.; Page No. 21; Position No. 1B; Name of Person or Group: Lowell Thomas Walters, 1
    - Verso: School name: Harrodsburg; City: Harrodsburg; State: KY.; Page No. 21; Position No. 1B; Name of Person or Group: Lowell Thomas Walters, 1-verso
    - [Namesakes:]Mechanic in School at Ft. Sill, Oklahoma last summer 1951 Lowell Thomas Christerson, 2
    - Verso: Mechanic in School at Ft. Sill, Oklahoma last summer 1951 Lowell Thomas Christerson, 2-verso
    - [Namesakes:]Lowell Thomas Frame 1953, 3
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas Frame 1953, 3-verso
    - [Namesakes:]Lowell Thomas Armstrong Class of '54', 4
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas Armstrong Class of '54', 4-verso
    - [Namesakes: Baby]Nov 16/51 11 months, 5
    - Verso: Nov 16/51 11 months, 5-verso
    - [Namesakes: Little boy with dog], 6
    - [Namesakes: Portrait of boy], 7
    - [Namesakes:]School Days 1962-63 Macon, 8
    - Verso: Lowell Hill 10 Years, 8-verso
    - [Namesakes: Little boy standing on bench in front of window], 9
    - Lowell Thomas Stupp; Born July 25, 1942; 3 Years an 3 mos in this picture this is the Best I have at Present, 10
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas Stupp; Born July 25, 1942; 3 Years an 3 mos in this picture this is the Best I have at Present, 10-verso
    - Lowell Thomas Cole; age 2; Oklahoma City Okla; Jan 31. 1951; J.C. Best M.D. 111 So. Bdway., 11
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas Cole; age 2; Oklahoma City Okla; Jan 31. 1951; J.C. Best M.D. 111 So. Bdway., 11-verso
  - Electra Ward Nicks [includes color photograph], circa 1960s - 1970s; 15 (Box 1615)
    - [Electra Ward Nicks: Portrait of woman], 1
    - [Electra Ward Nicks: Portrait of woman], 2
    - Note: I want this back-- for sure E-, 3
    - I want this back-- for sure E-, 4
    - Verso: Electra, 4-verso
    - L to R; L. Thomas; E. Nicks; L. Ross, 5
    - Verso: L to R; L. Thomas; E. Nicks; L. Ross, 5-verso
  - N - miscellaneous, undated; 16 (Box 1615)
    - [N-miscellaneous: Man and woman standing in front of fireplace], 1
  - Observatory, undated; 17 (Box 1615)
    - Dome of the 26-inch refracting telescope at the U.S. Naval Observatory., 1
    - Verso: Dome of the 26-inch refracting telescope at the U.S. Naval Observatory., 1-verso
    - [Observatory: Sketch of a scientific instrument], 2
    - [Observatory: Sketch of a scientific instrument], 3
    - [Observatory: Two men looking at instrument], 4
    - [Observatory: Man working on an instrument], 5
    - [Observatory: Men working with scientific instruments], 6
    - [Observatory: Men working with scientific instrument], 7
  - Poems to Pearl, undated; 18 (Box 1615)
    - [Poems to Pearl: Man leaning against tree], 1
  - Nepal [color photograph], undated; 19 (Box 1615)
    - Their Majesties on The Ancient Throne of Nepal Coronation Day, 1
  - Niagara University, 1968; 20 (Box 1615)
    - Note: identify these men in the pictures; Father Slattery on the left; The tall one - President of the Associasted Press; Under Secretary of Commerce who gave the commencement address..., 1
    - [Niagara University: Lowell Thomas and three other men in graduation caps and gowns], 2
    - [Niagara University: Lowell Thomas and group of men in graduation caps and gowns]June 1, 1968, 3
    - Verso: June 1, 1968, 3-verso
  - N - miscellaneous, 1928 March 12 - 1953 December 18; 21 (Box 1615)
    - [N-miscellaneous: Aerial view of neighborhood], 1
    - [N-miscellaneous: Portrait of a man]Bud, 2
    - Verso: William O. Nice, 2-verso
    - Nurses' Residence, New York Hospital, 3
    - Cornell Medical College-New York Hospital, 4
    - Mathew Hartnup Home; named after a famous old doctor in Middle Age, who lived here in 1670, 5
    - Verso: Mathew Hartnup Home; named after a famous old doctor in Middle Age, who lived here in 1670, 5-verso
    - The old cloth Hall; Smarden, 6
    - Verso: The old cloth Hall; Smarden, 6-verso
  - Pace University commencement, 1976 June; 22 (Box 1615)
    - Note[PDF]: June 21, 1976; Mr. Lowell Thomas; Pawling, New York; Dear Mr. Thomas: We thought you might enjoy seeing the enclosed photographs and clipping..., 1
    - Note[PDF]: June 15, 1976; Mrs. Electra Knicks; c/o Lowell Thomas; Hammersley Hill; Pawling, New York 12564; Dear Mrs. Knicks: Many thanks for your patience and thoughtfulness, 2
    - Mr. Lowell Thomas as commencement speaker on June 5 at Pace University, 3
    - [Lowell Thomas at Pace University Commencement], 4
  - Roy Parer, 1966 - 1974; 23 (Box 1615)
    - [Man (Roy Parer?) standing between two women in front of car], 1
  - Samuel Pryor, 1970 - 1980; 24 (Box 1615)
    - Sam Pryor; Secor Browne; Mary Tay; Secor's fiance Constance Haden, 1
    - Verso: Sam Pryor; Secor Browne; Mary Tay; Secor's fiance Constance Haden, 1-verso
    - Peace on Earth; Larry, Gaby, Ben & Will Pryor, 2
    - [Ben and Will Pryor(?) holding dog and cat]December 1980, 3
    - Verso: December 1980, 3-verso
  - Samuel and Sally Pryor, 1967 - 1976; 25 (Box 1615)
    - Joyeux Noel; The Pryors, 1
    - Verso: Save as bag. Insert, 1-verso
    - Mrs. Samuel F. Pryor III [address}, 2
    - Verso: Mrs. Samuel F. Pryor III [address}, 2-verso
  - Quaker Hill book, 1979 - 1981; 26 (Box 1615)
    - [Quaker Hill book: Portrait of man], 1
    - [Quaker Hill book: Portrait of man], 2
    - [Quaker Hill book: Man sitting in rocking chair with papers on his lap], 3
  - G. Srinivas Rao, 1964- 1977; 27 (Box 1615)
    - G. Srinivas Rao, 1
    - Birthday Greetings to Lowell Thomas- G. Srinivas Rao 1967, 2
    - To Lowell Thomas; With deepest regards- G. Srinivas Rao + family 1967, 3
    - Verso: To Lowell Thomas; With deepest regards- G. Srinivas Rao + family 1967, 3-verso
  - The Reader's Digest, circa 1960s - 1970s; 28 (Box 1615)
    - Gisele Devine; wife of C.R. (Bob) Devine; Reader's Digest, 1
    - Verso: Gisele Devine; wife of C.R. (Bob) Devine; Reader's Digest, 1-verso
  - Old food recipes (British), undated; 29 (Box 1615)
    - [Old food recipes (British):]Warne's Domestic CookeryFront Cover, 1
    - [Old food recipes (British):]Swinborne's Patent Refined Isinglass, Extra QualityBack Cover, 2
    - [Old food recipes (British):]Double Spread Showing Old Cookery Equipment, 3
  - Remote places, 1933- 1943; 30 (Box 1615)
    - [Remote places: Man with dog by a vehicle], 1
    - [Remote places: People by canoes and huts], 2
    - [Remote places: Boat on water], 3
    - [Remote places: Icey water and snowcapped mountains], 4
    - [Remote places:]The lake is not always as calm as this here!, 5
    - Verso: The lake is not always as calm as this here!, 5-verso
    - [Remote places:]This is the great Upsala Glacier which forms the Western boundry of our farm., 6
    - Verso: This is the great Upsala Glacier which forms the Western boundry of our farm., 6-verso
  - Oral Roberts, 1975 - 1980; 31 (Box 1615)
    - [Front of Card] Oral and Evelyn Roberts, 1
    - Verso: [inside of card] We make our Confession of Faith for yout spiritual, physical, financial, blessings this blessed Christmas. And we love you in Jesus's name. Oral and Evelyn, 1-verso
    - [Front of Card] Merry Christmas (Oral and Evelyn Roberts), 2
    - Verso: [inside of card] Glory to God in the highest, and on earth peace, good will toward men. -Luke 2:14 Oral and Evelyn, 2-verso
  - Cliff Robertson (The Spirit of St. Louis airplane), 1977; 32 (Box 1615)
    - Note: Dumont Studios; Pawling, New York [Envelope], 1
    - Charles A. Lindbergh, 2
    - Verso: Produced by: York Enterprises, Inc. 1 East 44th St., NY., NY 10017, 2-verso
    - Note: The Commemorative Medallion for the CHARLES A. LINDBERG MEMORIAL FUND established to raise $5 million for fellowship and grants in aeronautics research, 3
    - CLIFF ROBERTSON interviews JOHN VANDERLINDE who was the Chief Field Mechanic at Ryan Aviation, San Diego, and worked with Charles Lindbergh in the building and testing of the Spirit of St. Louis, 4
    - Verso: Produced by: York Enterprises, Inc. 1 East 44th St., NY., NY 10017, 4-verso
    - Note[PDF]: CLIFF ROBERTSON interviews JOHN VANDERLINDE who was the Chief Field Mechanic at Ryan Aviation, San Diego, and worked with Charles Lindbergh in the building and testing of the Spirit of St. Louis, 5
    - [Cliff Robertson: Man standing in front of airplane that reads "Spirit of St. Louis II"], 6
    - [Cliff Robertson: Man looking out of airplane window, smiling], 7
    - [Cliff Robertson: Man standing in front of the "Spirit of St. Louis II" airplane], 8
    - [Cliff Robertson: Man leaning against a two-seater airplane], 9
    - [Cliff Robertson: Man standing in front of "Spirit of St. Louis II" airplane], 10
    - [Cliff Robertson: Older gentleman standing in front of the "Spirit of St. Louis II" airplane], 11
    - [Cliff Robertson: Two men standing in front of the "Spirit of St. Louis II" airplane], 12
    - [Cliff Robertson: Two men standing in front of the "Spirit of St. Louis II" airplane], 13
    - [Cliff Robertson: Man in flight gear, leaning against airplane, smiling], 14
    - [Cliff Robertson: Group of people with camera equipment standing around "Spirit of St. Louis II" airplane], 15
  - Rockwell Polar Flight, 1965; 33 (Box 1615)
    - [Rockwell Polar Flight:]Left to Right: (Seated) Fred Austing, Capt. Bob Buck, Jack Martin (SR Pilot), Harrison Finch. (Standing) Velazza, Larson, Degroot, Capt. Gannett, Olson, Jones, Hinchman. Flight crew of the Boeing 707 "Polecat" Experimental and Technical Research Flight, November 17, 1965..., 1
    - Note[PDF]: [Rockwell Polar Flight:] Left to Right: (Seated) Fred Austing, Capt. Bob Buck, Jack Martin (SR Pilot), Harrison Finch. (Standing) Velazza, Larson, Degroot, Capt. Gannett, Olson, Jones, Hinchman. Flight crew of the Boeing 707 "Polecat" Experimental and Technical Research Flight, November 17, 1965..., 2
    - [Rockwell Polar Flight:]Front Row, Kneeling or Sitting on Runway, Left to Right: Sande, Furuya, P. Mesquita, J. Eyerman (Life), J. Demuth, 3
    - Note[PDF]: [Rockwell Polar Flight:] Front Row, Kneeling or Sitting on Runway, Left to Right: Sande, Furuya, P. Mesquita, J. Eyerman (Life), J. Demuth, 4
    - [Rockwell Polar Flight: Group of men gathered for a picture in front of the "Flying Tiger" airplane], 5
    - [Rockwell Polar Flight: Group of men gathered for a picture in front of the "Flying Tiger" airplane], 6
  - Rose [The Lowell Thomas rose], undated; 34 (Box 1615)
    - Number: CP41-3; Subject: Rose; Variety: Lowell Thomas, 1
    - Verso: Number: CP41-3; Subject: Rose; Variety: Lowell Thomas, 1-verso
  - N. G. Rutgers, Jr., 1976; 35 (Box 1615)
    - Greetings from the Rugters; Aspen, Colo. 1976, 1
  - Joseph Ryan, 1938 - 1947; 36 (Box 1615)
    - [Joseph Ryan: Men building a house], 1
    - [Joseph Ryan: Type of infrastructure], 2
    - [Joseph Ryan: Men building a house], 3
    - [Joseph Ryan: Men building a house], 4
    - [Joesph Ryan: Men working on a foundation], 5
    - [Joseph Ryan: Type of construction equipment(?)], 6
  - John Ryer, undated; 37 (Box 1615)
    - [John Ryer: People wake boarding (?)], 1
  - Sahuaro Ski Club, circa 1940s; 38 (Box 1615)
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club: Man on skiis], 1
    - Verso: Thomas, 1-verso
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club: Two men on snowy hillside], 2
    - Verso: Kpupy [?], 2-verso
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club: Man airbourne on skiis], 3
    - Verso: Thomas, 3-verso
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club: Man airbourne on skiis], 4
    - Verso: Kempy [?], 4-verso
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club: Snow, man skiing], 5
    - Verso: Thomas, 5-verso
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club: Four men in a line on skiis, Lowell Thomas second to last], 6
    - [Sahuaro Ski Club: Three men in a line on skiis], 7
  - John P. and Gladys Sawyer, 1980; 39 (Box 1615)
    - Mele Kalikimaka; John and Laurie; Jessica, Parker, Holly, 1
    - Verso: Aloha! We're having a wonderful time with "Nane" and "Popa" Sawyer here, 1-verso
    - [John P. and Gladys Sawyer: Portrait of a dog], 2
  - John P. Sawyer, 1959 - 1964; 40 (Box 1615)
    - [John P. Sawyer: Woman in a fur coat], 1
    - [John P. Sawyer: Woman in a fur coat], 2
    - [John P. Sawyer: Woman in a fur coat], 3
    - [John P. Sawyer: Woman in a fur coat], 4
  - Willy Schaefler and Lowell Thomas, undated; 41 (Box 1615)
    - [Willy Schaefler (?) and Lowell Thomas], 1
  - Schedules, 1980; 42 (Box 1615)
    - [Schedules: Close-up of Lowell Thomas], 1
  Box 1616
- Topical files 1, 2.1.9.4
  - Adelaide Scott and Lowell Thomas, 1967; 1 (Box 1616)
    - [Adelaide Scott (?) and Lowell Thomas standing together and smiling], 1
    - Verso: Scott, 1-verso
    - [Adelaide Scott (?) and Lowell Thomas standing together and smiling], 2
  - Ronald and Judy Senykoff, circa 1970s; 2 (Box 1616)
    - Ron and Judy Senykoff, 1
    - Verso: Ron and Judy Senykoff, 1-verso
  - Elliott Sluhan - Focus Unlimited, 1960 - 1981; 3 (Box 1616)
    - Note: Sluhan Family, 1
    - Sluhan Family, 2
    - 1. Mr. Leon Gorman, President of L. L. Bean, Inc., the Freeport, Maine, outfitter and Woolrich President, Mr. Roswell Brayton, 3
    - Verso[PDF]: 1. Mr. Leon Gorman, President of L. L. Bean, Inc., the Freeport, Maine, outfitter and Woolrich President, Mr. Roswell Brayton, 3-verso
  - Frank M. Smith, 1956 January; 4 (Box 1616)
    - [Frank M. Smith: Portrait of a man (Frank M. Smith?)], 1
    - [Frank M. Smith: Portrait of a man (Frank M. Smith?)], 2
    - [Frank M. Smith: Portrait of a man (Frank M. Smith?)], 3
    - [Frank M. Smith: Portrait of a man (Frank M. Smith?)], 4
    - [Frank M. Smith: Portrait of a man (Frank M. Smith?)], 5
    - [Frank M. Smith: Portrait of a man (Frank M. Smith?)], 6
    - [Frank M. Smith: Portrait of a man (Frank M. Smith?)], 7
    - [Frank M. Smith: Portrait of a man (Frank M. Smith?)], 8
    - Verso: CBS Photo-Urgo, 8-verso
    - [Frank M. Smith: Portrait of a man (Frank M. Smith?)], 9
    - Verso: CBS Photo-Urgo, 9-verso
    - [Frank M. Smith: Portrait of a man (Frank M. Smith?)], 10
    - Verso: CBS Photo-Urgo, 10-verso
    - [Frank M. Smith: Portrait of a man (Frank M. Smith?)], 11
    - Verso: CBS Photo-Urgo, 11-verso
  - South America-Take to.., 1961 October 2; 5 (Box 1616)
    - [South America-Take to..:]September 1961; It is I, walking with my 2 mountain sticks and the best Peruvian painter, Manuel Zapata, 1
    - Verso: September 1961; It is I, walking with my 2 mountain sticks and the best Peruvian painter, Manuel Zapata, 1-verso
  - Silas Strawn, 1968 April 16 - 1969 July 9; 6 (Box 1616)
    - [Silas Strawn: Framed portrait of a man (Silas Strawn?)], 1
    - [Silas Strawn: Framed portrait of a man (Silas Strawn?)], 2
    - [Silas Strawn: Framed note entitled "Tribute to Silas Strawn"], 3
    - [Silas Strawn: Framed note entitled "Tribute to Silas Strawn"], 4
    - [Silas Strawn:]Mt. Brooks; Muldrow Glacier; Mt. McKinley by Lincoln Washburn; Airplane; 1935; The right half of this picture with Muldrow Glacier in foreground, 5
    - Verso: Mt. Brooks; Muldrow Glacier; Mt. McKinley by Lincoln Washburn; Airplane; 1935; The right half of this picture with Muldrow Glacier in foreground, 5-verso
    - [Silas Strawn:]Mt. McKinley from Wonder Lake; 1933; Mt. Brooks to the left, 6
    - Verso: Mt. McKinley from Wonder Lake; 1933; Mt. Brooks to the left, 6-verso
    - [Silas Strawn: Close-up of a man (Silas Strawn?)], 7
    - Verso: Bruno Engler, Alpine Films, Baniff-Alta, 7-verso
    - [Silas Strawn:]Mt. McKinley; N and S peaks, 8
    - Verso: Mt. McKinley; N and S peaks, 8-verso
    - [Silas Strawn:]Taken from airplain; Mt. McKinley; Shows both peaks, 9
    - Verso: Taken from airplain; Mt. McKinley; Shows both peaks, 9-verso
  - Erling Strom party, 1966; 7 (Box 1616)
    - [Erling Strom party: (Three photos) People seated at dining tables], 1
    - [Erling Strom party: (Three photos) People seated at dining tables], 2
    - [Erling Strom party: (Two photos) People seated at dining tables], 3
    - [Erling Strom party: (Two photos) People seated at dining tables], 4
    - [Erling Strom party: (Two photos) People seated at dining tables], 5
    - [Erling Strom party: (Three photos) People seated at dining tables], 6
    - [Erling Strom party: (Two photos) Man at microphone], 7
    - [Erling Strom party: Close-up of a man wearing a hat, Earl Strom,]1956. Don't Return!, 8
    - Verso: 1956. Don't Return!, 8-verso
    - [Erling Strom party: Man at microphone with banjo], 9
    - [Erlign Strom party: People at dining tables], 10
    - [Erling Strom party: People at dining tables, man standing], 11
    - [Erling Strom party: People at dining tables, man at microphone], 12
    - [Erling Strom party: People at dining tables], 13
    - [Erling Strom party: People at dining tables], 14
    - [Erling Strom party: People at dining tables], 15
    - [Erling Strom party: People at dining tables], 16
    - [Erling Strom party: People at dining tables, man standing], 17
    - [Erling Strom party: Close-up of man, Earl Strom, wearing a hat], 18
    - [Erling Strom party: Close-up of man, Earl Strom, wearing a hat], 19
    - [Erling Strom party: Close-up of man, Earl Strom, wearing a hat], 20
    - Lake Placid Club; Group of skiers around fire place; Earl Strom in pic, 21
    - Verso: Lake Placid Club; Group of skiers around fire place; Earl Strom in pic, 21-verso
    - Earl Strom, 22
    - Verso: Earl Strom, 22-verso
    - [Framed portrait of]Mr. Erling Strom, 23
    - Verso: Mr. Erling Strom, 23-verso
  - S - miscellaneous, 1970 - 1981; 8 (Box 1616)
    - [S-miscellaneous: Group of people wearing skiis posing for a picture], 1
    - We Pick You For Our Valentine; The Stadlers, 2
    - Verso[PDF]: Greetings from the Ohio farm country, although, this picture was taken at Christmas in gradmother's backyard in Boca Raton, 2-verso
    - Note: William v. Stelling zu Langensalza-Stellinggen-Wetten; The Stelling-Langensalza-Stelligen part of it is around Hamburg, 3
    - Note: Mr. Lowell Thomas; "Main Top" Hammersley, 4
    - William v. Stelling zu Langensalza-Stellinggen-Wetten; The Stelling-Langensalza-Stelligen part of it is around Hamburg, 5
    - William v. Stelling zu Langensalza-Stellinggen-Wetten; The Stelling-Langensalza-Stelligen part of it is around Hamburg, 6
  - Clif Taylor, undated; 9 (Box 1616)
    - [Clif Taylor: Man on skiis], 1
    - Verso: l.s. Colemanm Photographer, 1-verso
    - [Clif Taylor: Man on skiis in front of group of people on skiis], 2
    - Verso: l.s. Colemanm Photographer, 2-verso
  - Clif Taylor (Shortee Skis), 1960s; 10 (Box 1616)
    - Clif Taylor on Shortee 2 1/2 [?] Weden Skis, 1
    - Verso: Clif Taylor on Shortee 2 1/2 [?] Weden Skis, 1-verso
    - Louisa Taylor 3 year old daughter of Clif-likes her daddy's short [?] 2 1/2 [?] Weden Skis-Complete with stand and nylon cord for carrying, 2
    - Verso: Louisa Taylor 3 year old daughter of Clif-likes her daddy's short [?] 2 1/2 [?] Weden Skis-Complete with stand and nylon cord for carrying, 2-verso
  - Kesang Tenduf-la, 1962; 11 (Box 1616)
    - [Kesang Tenduf-la:]Elizabeth; aged 3 yrs. Rota, Spain; June 1962, 1
    - Verso: Elizabeth; aged 3 yrs. Rota, Spain; June 1962, 1-verso
    - [Kesang Tenduf-la:]Ann-10 mos.; Rota, Spain; June 1962, 2
    - Verso: Ann-10 mos.; Rota, Spain; June 1962, 2-verso
  - H. T. (Henry) Thomas, 1966; 12 (Box 1616)
    - [H. T. (Henry) Thomas: Painting of a ship on water], 1
    - [H. T. (Henry) Thomas:]20"x 24"; Hawaiian National Flower; by Hat; 1966., 2
    - Verso: 20"x 24"; Hawaiian National Flower; by Hat; 1966., 2-verso
  - Lowell Thomas family, undated; 13 (Box 1616)
    - [Lowell Thomas family:]Merry Christmas; Janet and Frank West, 1
    - Verso: Have a Merry Christmas in Alaska-Love-Janet, 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas family:]Note: Marion F. West [address], 2
  - Max W. Thornburg and Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, circa 1960s; 14 (Box 1616)
    - [Max W. Thornburg and Mrs. Frances Ryan (?) standing together outside], 1
    - Note: Max Thornburg file; this is the kind of cigars he smokes, 2
  - Peter Townsend, undated; 15 (Box 1616)
    - Best Wishes for Christmas and a Happy New Year; [?] + Peter Townsend [address], 1
    - Verso: Best Wishes for Christmas and a Happy New Year; [?] + Peter Townsend [address], 1-verso
  - Television letters, 1975; 16 (Box 1616)
    - Note: Merry Christmas + Happy New Year; I like your new TV series-I had a great year in '75'; Phil, 1
    - [Television letters: Statue of a man riding in a horse-drawn carraige], 2
  - Television series (Lowell Thomas Remembers), 1970s; 17 (Box 1616)
    - PBS Lowell Thomas during an informal chat with President Franklin D. Roosevelt, 1
    - PBS "So long until tomorrow," says the host of LOWELL THOMAS REMEMBERS on PBS, 2
    - PBS Lowell Thomas, host of LOWELL THOMAS REMEMBERS on PBS..., 3
  - Twentieth anniversary, 1930 - 1950; 18 (Box 1616)
    - [Twentieith anniversary: Two women and a man sitting on a beach], 1